

UI/UX Designer

www.saharfeyz.com sahar.fe.design@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am highly interested in creative, meaningful, and human-centered designs. Throughout my university education I learned that understanding the target audience, their needs, and the affordances are crucial in intuitive and effective design. I learned to research and build user-flows, personas, customer journey frameworks, and prototypes. Also, I am detail-oriented, and from my work experience I was able to build interpersonal and leadership skills.

EDUCATION

B. A. INTERACTIVE ARTS & TECHNOLOGY
Simon Fraser University BC Canada
Summer 2014 - Fall 2019

SOFTWARE SKILLS

HTML Adobe (Photoshop, CSS Illustrator, InDesign, Principle XD, Lightroom, Sketch Premier Pro, Bridge, Axure After Effects) Figma Arduino InVision Processing Mava JavaScript CorelDraw Rhino Balsamiq SolidWorks

SKILLS

Sketching Responsive web Ideation design Heuristic Wireframing Evaluation Customer Journey Framework Storyboarding Iterative process Research Physical/Digital Illustration Design thinking Prototyping

User testing

3D Rendering

WORK EXPERIENCE

HERE2HELP APP BC Canada **UI/UX Designer**

Dec 2020 - May 2021

NATURALIZER (BRENTWOOD TOWN CENTER) BC Canada

Assistant Manager

NATURALIZER (COQUITLAM CENTER)
BC Canada

Assistant Manager

Sep 2012 - June 2016

Design Evaluation

TIP TOP TAILORS (COQUITLAM CENTER) BC Canada

Assistant Manager

Nov 2016 - March 2021

Sept 2009 - Oct 2012